const quiz = [
  {
    question: "If you are in an intersection and you hear the siren of an emergency vehicle, you should",
    answers: [
      {content: "move to the right and stop in the intersection"}, 
      {content: "continues through the intersection, then move to the left and stop"}, 
      {content: "move to the left and stop in the intersection"}, 
      {content: "continue through the intersection, then move to the right and stop"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "continue through the intersection, then move to the right and stop"    
  }, {
    question: "A driver who is a minor receives a phone call on his or her cell phone. He or she should",
    answers: [
      {content: "not answer the call."},
      {content: "use a hands-free cell phone to answer the call."},
      {content: "answer the call in an emergency."},
      {content: "not be carrying a cell phone while driving"},
    ],
    correctAnswer: "not answer the call.",
  }, {
    question: "A traffic signal with a flashing yellow arrow means that you should.",
    answers: [
      {content: "proceed at increased speed as directed by the arrow."},
      {content: "proceed with caution."},
      {content: "proceed with caution but turns are not permitted in the direction of the arrow."},
      {content: "stop and be prepared to obey the next signal."},
    ],    
    correctAnswer: "proceed with caution.",
  }, {
    question: "A driver who is involved in a collision should report it to the DMV within.",
    answers: [
      {content:"20 days."},
      {content: "10 days."},
      {content: "30 days."},
      {content: "15 days."},
    ],
    correctAnswer: "10 days."    
  }, {
    question: "What is the first thing you should do during an enforcement stop?",
    answers: [
      {content:"Stop on the left shoulder."},
      {content: "Stop on the center median."},
      {content: "Turn on your right turn signal."},
      {content: "Turn on your left turn signal."},
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Turn on your right turn signal."    
  }, {
    question: "While driving in fog, you should use your",
    answers: [
      {content:"low-beam headlights."},
      {content: "emergency signals."},
      {content: "high-beam headlights."},
      {content: "parking lights."},
    ],
    correctAnswer: "low-beam headlights."    
  },  {
    question: "A driver in front of you is signaling with his or her hand and arm pointing upwards. This driver wants to",
    answers: [
      {content:"slow down."},
      {content: "turn right."},
      {content: "turn left."},
      {content: "stop."},
    ],
    correctAnswer: "turn right."    
  },  {
    question: "When you see livestock near the roadway, you should",
    answers: [
      {content:"blow your horn continuously until the animals cross the road."},
      {content: "turn safely away from these animals."},
      {content: "follow directions from the person in charge of the animals."},
      {content: "signal the person in charge of the animals to move right."},
    ],
    correctAnswer: "follow directions from the person in charge of the animals."    
  }, {
    question: "When you want to enter a freeway, you should",
    answers: [
      {content:"stop before merging into freeway traffic."},
      {content: "enter the freeway at or near the speed of freeway traffic."},
      {content: "enter the freeway at a minimum speed."},
      {content: "stop and yield to the traffic on the freeway."},
    ],
    correctAnswer: "enter the freeway at or near the speed of freeway traffic."    
  }, {
    question: "If you litter on the roadside, you are subject to a fine of ",
    answers: [
      {content:"$600."},
      {content: "$1,500."},
      {content: "$500."},
      {content: "$1,000."},
    ],
    correctAnswer: "$1,000."    
  },{
    question: "Special 'turnout' areas marked on a two-lane road",
    answers: [
      {content:"allow vehicles to make U-turns."},
      {content: "allow drivers to stop and talk on their cell phones."},
      {content: "allow vehicles to make left turns."},
      {content: "allow vehicles to pass."},
    ],
    correctAnswer: "allow vehicles to pass."    
  },
]

export default quiz;